<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="vc_0">Dear Students,</string>
     <string name="vc_1">
                I wish to welcome both returning and all our fresh student to the serene and student friendly campus
                of the Nigerian Turkish Nile university for the new academic session, I wish to congratulate the returning
                students on their success at the last session"\u0027"s examination. I also rejoice with the fresh students on their admission to the University this session. </string>

     <string name="vc_2">
                
                You have passed through a period and entered into a new level where you will be held accountable for
                your life via quality of education acquired here. I assured you that the quality of education delivery at NTNU
                is of international standard.</string>

    <string name="vc_3">
                The need to provide both the returning and fresh students with adequate and current information on the activities of the University in order to bridge communication gap informed the review of the existing student’s handbook. This handbook is an authoritative source of information necessary for the guidance of all students throughout the duration of their stay in the University. Therefore all students should endeavour to collect the handbook from their various Departments, study and acquaint themselves with information therein.</string>
    <string name="vc_4">It is pertinent for all new students to note that the various activities (both social and academic) engaged in while on campus, will earn points that would cumulatively reflect in the final transcript.</string>

    <string name="vc_5">NTNU is in collaboration with many International Universities. Recently, we signed special MoUs with two International Universities to embark on exchange programmes. This is an opportunity to be explored by students. Students should research the courses available for the exchange programme and discover new internship opportunities to enhance practical exposure and widen their knowledge and experience.</string>


    <string name="vc_6">Students should take advantage of the language courses offered at NTNU to develop themselves, be relevant and impactful on the multi-cultural African society and the world at large. These language courses could be taken as minors or part of double majors; the opportunities are endless here.</string>


    <string name="vc_7">New students should ensure that they attend the yearly orientation program conducted by the University at the beginning of their academic semester.  This program affords them the opportunity of meeting the Heads of Departments (HoDs) officially, for the first time. It is also at this gathering that they will get acquainted with the University general rules and regulations, lecture venues, libraries, etc.</string>

    <string name="vc_8">In fact, it is important to establish and maintain cordial relationship with your Heads of Departments (HoDs). Endeavour to check the H.O.D’s office and notice boards from time to time to be abreast of current events at the department.</string>

    <string name="vc_9">I wish to inform all fresh students that NTNU offers the opportunity for them to network and make friends with people from various nationalities, cultural backgrounds and professions. One avenue where contacts can be established is in the University social clubs.</string>

    <string name="vc_10">Interested students who wish to take advantage of the existence of the various social clubs in the University to develop their hobbies, leadership and inherent skills and make friends are advised to contact the Student Affairs Division for guidance. It is our expectation that all your energies, time and resources will always be directed to things that are noble and constructive.
</string>

    <string name="vc_11">Students should feel free to visit the career planning centres to be informed about prospective job offers. You should also participate in the activities of the Alumni Association to keep in touch with your friends even after graduation.</string>

    <string name="vc_12">To the returning students, time passes swiftly, and your University education will be completed in a short time. It is only imperative that you learn to use all the detailed information acquired from your lecturers, library (research), information technology, and even from this website effectively. Get relevant information about e-learning and distant education programs that can be of use to you in future.</string>

    <string name="vc_13">Keep track of activities in the University and actively participate in them; take notes, and ask questions. Try to attend programmes organized by different Departments and Faculties related to your course of study.</string>

    <string name="vc_14">I am very delighted to inform you that the School of Postgraduate Studies has taken off and hope you will take advantage of it to do your master programme here.
</string>

    <string name="vc_15">Globalisation has reached the point of ‘localisation’ lately, in which local features are considered while trying to think and act globally. In other words, while being global on one hand, do not forget your local values, traditions, cultures, society and language on the other hand. That is why at NTNU, we also pay attention to your moral, social, ethical and religious development.</string>

    <string name="vc_16">Dear students, let me emphasize here that there is no short road to any place worth going because only a serious approach can guarantee a glorious and excellent result. That is, to be successful, the opportunity you have to study at NTNU must be consolidated with adequate preparation.</string>

    <string name="vc_17">Once again, I welcome all new students to NTNU and wish you all success in 2015/2016 academic year.
</string>

    <string name="vc_18">Prof. Dr. Huseyin Sert M.D</string>

    <string name="vc_19">Vice Chancellor,</string>
	<string name="vc_20">Nigerian Turkish Nile University</string>

</resources>